KRITIK VERMA

MARKETING

 \sim

kritik3b@gmail.com

C

9718305545

9

Delhi, India 110070

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced marketing professional with a strong drive to contribute to team success through diligent work ethic, meticulous attention to detail, and exceptional organizational skills. Demonstrates comprehensive understanding of various marketing strategies, including SEO, campaign development, and social media management. Highly motivated to continuously learn, grow, and excel in the dynamic industry.

SKILLS

SEO best practices

SEO coding and strategy

Campaign development

Email marketing

Collaboration

Social media

Performance marketing

Paid marketing

Keyword optimization

EDUCATION

Middlesex University

Dubai • 09/2022 - 09/2023

MSc: Digital Marketing And Analytics

Institute of Management Studies Ghaziabad • 04/2018 - 04/2020

PGDM/MBA: Marketing

College of Vocational Studies
Delhi • 03/2015 - 03/2018

Bachelor Of Arts: Marketing

WORK HISTORY

Mobikasa - SEO Specialist Delhi • 12/2024 - Current

- Analyzed SEO audit and fixed issues for the clients.
- Improved website traffic by implementing effective SEO strategies like content, keyword optimization, schema etc.
- Working on multiple clients and handling the end to end SEO and communication.
- Implemented best practices in SEO and recommended client about implementation of new tactics.

Instaacoders Technologies Pvt Ltd - SEO Executive Delhi. India • 02/2024 - 08/2024

- Reduced SEO errors by working on SEO audit report, using informed decision making in day to day tasks thereby improving user experience.
- Managed successful link-building campaigns, securing high-quality backlinks.
- Conducted backlink analysis to inform strategic decision-making processes and fixed broken links.
- Stayed up-to-date with Google core updates and keeping in mind the Google statements and did SEO reporting.

7awi - Social Media and SEO Executive (Freelance Contract) Dubai , UAE • 02/2023 - 07/2023

- Handling social and SEO accounts of clients simultaneously.
- Brainstorming and making social calendars with concept ideas for social media content and scheduling posts.
- Using AI in brainstorming content ideas and copywriting. Gained insight to App marketing, push notification and social media community.
- Delivering project deliverables on time in terms of social media and digital marketing.

Real Time Data Services Pvt Ltd (RTDS) - Online Marketing/SEO Executive

St Paul's School

Delhi • 02/2014 - 02/2015

12th: Humanities

SOFTWARE

WordPress

Upper intermediate

Yoast SEO

Upper intermediate

SEM Rush

Upper intermediate

Buffer

Intermediate

Zoho CRM

Intermediate

Hubspot

Intermediate

CERTIFICATIONS

09/2021

PG certificate in digital marketing from MICA.

08/2020

Advanced digital marketing from Crea8tify.

Gurugram , Haryana • 08/2021 - 08/2022

- Managing postings and engagement by developing captions and hashtags thereby implementing different social media tips for client that resulted in enhanced marketing efforts.
- Reviewing and recommending the performance of Google Search Console, Moz, SEMrush etc.
- Exceeded goals through effective task prioritization and great work ethic. Met deadlines and expectations by effectively rolling out influencer marketing and guest posts.
- Maximized strategic approaches by keeping a close eye on performance marketing and making appropriate adjustments using Zoho CRM, Mouse flow, GTM and Google analytics.

Elixir Web Solutions - Jr SEO Executive

New Delhi , Delhi • 01/2021 - 08/2021

- Reviewed and optimized client sites to improve keyword targeting,
 URL strategies, website architecture and content.
- Analyzed and audited clients' website and Completed keyword research to target client based on keyword targeting.
- Utilized and emphasized importance of backlink auditing and outreach to add value.
- Created email blast campaigns and testing on key customers through MailChimp and Get Response.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Meritorious Student Award for class 12.
- · Spotlight award and going extra mile award at RTDS.